<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.0">Jekyll</generator><link href="elee.page/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="elee.page/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2022-01-25T21:46:12+09:00</updated><id>elee.page/feed.xml</id><title type="html">blog</title><entry><title type="html">About Eugene</title><link href="elee.page/blog/2022/01/25/About-Eugene/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="About Eugene" /><published>2022-01-25T00:00:00+09:00</published><updated>2022-01-25T00:00:00+09:00</updated><id>elee.page/blog/2022/01/25/About-Eugene</id><content type="html" xml:base="elee.page/blog/2022/01/25/About-Eugene/">&lt;h3 id=&quot;introduction&quot;&gt;Introduction&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;div class=&quot;figure&quot;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;column&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/media/image/2021-10-ELee.jpg&quot; style=&quot;width: 31%; float: left; display: block; margin: 0 auto;&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;column&quot;&gt;
    &lt;img src=&quot;/media/image/2022-01-ELee.jpeg&quot; style=&quot;width: 55%; float: left; display: block; margin: 0 auto;&quot; /&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;caption&quot;&gt;
        &lt;span class=&quot;caption-label&quot;&gt;Figure 1 (Left): Approximation of Eugene visualized. His photographer applied a lot of convolution layers. &lt;/span&gt; 
    &lt;/div&gt;
    &lt;div class=&quot;caption&quot;&gt;
        &lt;span class=&quot;caption-label&quot;&gt;Figure 2 (Right): Another approximation of Eugene at his natural habitat. &lt;/span&gt;
    &lt;/div&gt; 
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am a first-year graduate student at Korea University’s school of Artificial Intelligence in the &lt;a href=&quot;https://sites.google.com/view/sungjoon-choi/home&quot;&gt;Robot Intelligence Lab&lt;/a&gt;. As a first-year student, my current research interests are relatively broad - I am interested in improving the sample efficiency of Reinforcement Learning techniques or finding representations for learning that are effective for solving robotic tasks across multiple domains.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Before starting my graduate degree, I was a Machine Learning Engineer at &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.liftigniter.com/blog/our-new-chapter-begins&quot;&gt;LiftIgniter&lt;/a&gt;, a YC startup that provides recommendations as a service. At LiftIgniter, I spent most of my time delving into information retrieval, predictive analysis, and machine learning techniques related to recommendation systems, along with general software engineering and web architecture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prior to that, I completed BSc in Applied Mathematics and BA in Mathematics at Brown University. You can verify my credential &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.brown.edu/about/administration/registrar/cediplomas/validate-diploma&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;. Use &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;15C0-B3DB-E2E3&lt;/code&gt; for CeDiD code and &lt;code class=&quot;language-plaintext highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;EU&lt;/code&gt; for the first two letters of my name.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My life further back is complicated, so I’ll end here since we are running out of space; I was born in the United States, nurtured in Denmark, and raised in South Korea.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Introduction Figure 1 (Left): Approximation of Eugene visualized. His photographer applied a lot of convolution layers. Figure 2 (Right): Another approximation of Eugene at his natural habitat. I am a first-year graduate student at Korea University’s school of Artificial Intelligence in the Robot Intelligence Lab. As a first-year student, my current research interests are relatively broad - I am interested in improving the sample efficiency of Reinforcement Learning techniques or finding representations for learning that are effective for solving robotic tasks across multiple domains.</summary></entry></feed>